mitsubishielectric.com 2013-05-17

# MITSUBISHI ELECTRIC - Privacy Statement

### Commitment to Privacy on the Internet

Mitsubishi Electric Corporation is sensitive to privacy issues on the Internet. This policy explains how Mitsubishi Electric Corporation treats the information about you that we receive on the Internet. The purpose of this privacy policy is to inform you, as a visitor to our website (the "Site"), what kind of information we may gather about you when you visit this Site, how we may use that information, and whether we disclose it to anyone.

### Scope of Application

This privacy statement applies to Mitsubishi Electric Corporation and the Mitsubishi Electric Global Website ( <http://www.mitsubishielectric.com/> ). The statement does not apply to other companies' or organizations' websites to which the Site links.

### Non-Personal Information

In general, you can visit this Site without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. However we may automatically (i.e., not by registration) collect information that is not personally identifiable to help us provide better customer service. Our service automatically gathers certain information such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to the Site but we do so in ways that keep that information anonymous. This information is aggregated to measure the number of visits, average time spent on the Site and how much of the Site you use, so that we can improve our Site. We do not review information on individuals themselves. Mitsubishi Electric Corporation may use a technology nicknamed "cookies" that indicates how and when pages in the Site are visited, and by how many people. A cookie is an element of data that a website can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your system but does not collect personally identifiable information. You can set your browser to notify you before you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it or not. You can also set your browser to turn off cookies. If you do so, however, some areas of some sites may not function properly.

### Personal Information

Mitsubishi Electric Corporation fully complies with Japan's laws and regulations, national policies and other rules concerning the protection of personal information.

Personal information can be defined as any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address, an e-mail address or other contact information. 

Mitsubishi Electric Corporation sometimes collects personal information from its customers while conducting business activities. On the Global Website, personal information is collected predominantly through the various contact/inquiry forms.

When we directly solicit personal information from you in writing, we will specify how we intend to use the information, and ask for your consent. When we collect personal information by other means, we will announce on our website how we intend to use it.

When you provide us with personal information, we use the information to respond to and confirm your inquiry, and may keep a record of the inquiry for the same purposes. In addition, to support our customer relationship, we may store and process personal information and share it with our worldwide subsidiaries and affiliates to better understand your needs and how we can improve our products and services.

At times Mitsubishi Electric Corporation may conduct online surveys to better understand the needs and profile of our visitors. When we conduct a survey, we will do our utmost to let you know how we will use the information collected from you. Our site may provide contests, sweepstakes or other promotions that may ask you to enter your personal information. We will use the information you provide for the purpose of conducting the promotion, like providing customer support or contacting you if you're a winner.

Mitsubishi Electric Corporation does not use or disclose information gathered from individual visits to the Site or information that you may give us to any third parties for intention to sell, rent or otherwise market your personal information. We may at times employ a third party service providers to perform or assist us on the on-line surveys, contests, sweepstakes or other promotions. For example, administering the survey or promotion, compiling the data or providing customer support. These parties will have signed a Non-Disclosure Agreement prior to any services we initiate with them. They will not disclose any personal information they receive from you and will only use it in order to initiate and or continue the services they are providing for us.

You have the option not to provide personal information to Mitsubishi Electric Corporation. If you choose not to provide the personal information we request, you can still visit most of the Site, but you may be unable to access certain options, offers and services that involve our interaction with you. 

Click here for more information on how we manage personal information.

### Children

Children without the consent of their parent or guardian should not submit personal Information to the Site. While few, if any, of the materials of the Sites are directed towards children, Mitsubishi Electric Corporation encourages all parents or guardians to instruct their children in the safe and responsible use of their personal information while using the Internet.

### Notification of Changes

If Mitsubishi Electric Corporation decides to change our privacy statement, we will post those changes on this section so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone.

### Questions or Comments

It is important to us to hear what visitors have to say about our services, and our policies. If you have any questions, concerns, about this privacy statement, or anything about our off-line and on-line products and services, please contact the Webmaster at 'Contact Us'

### Your Consent

By using this Site, you consent to the terms of our privacy statement and to our collecting and processing of personal information for the purposes given above.
